

Profile

With 5 years of experience in full stack and blockchain development, I am a passionate and determined developer. My goal is to continue learning and excelling in the field of blockchain, in order to actively contribute to this rapidly expanding ecosystem.

Languages

French, English

Interests

Technology and Innovation Blockchain Finance Real Estate Sports

Info

- pellabeuf@gmail.com
- Paris, France
- in Linkedin
- Github
- Medium
- **X** Twitter

Foulques Pellabeuf

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

Technical Skills

Programming Languages

JavaScript NestJs Grafana Solidity TypeScript SQL/NOSQL Rust Elasticsearch React/Next.js Sequelize Circom **AWS** Noir-lang Angular **TypeORM** HTML/CSS Prisma Hardhat/Forge Tailwind Ethers.js/Wagmi GraphQL

> Redis Docker

Experiences

Bootstrap

Onbrane

2023 - Present

Lead Blockchain Developer

I develop a decentralized financial application EVM, using cryptographic techniques such as ZKP and homomorphic encryption to ensure the privacy of debt products.

Subgraph

Hexalabs

2022 - 2023

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

I developed frontends with React.js and Next.js, deployed blockchain projects in Solidity (DeFi, NFT Marketplace, etc.), and configured backends.

Toys films

2020 - 2022

Full Stack Developer

With Angular and various node.js frameworks, I designed innovative solutions for major clients such as L'Oréal, Microsoft, and Air Liquide.

Education

Hetic

2017 - 2020

Bachelor's in Real-time 3D

Training focused on real-time 3D content creation, covering applied mathematics and web development.